linkexchanged.com 2011-01-07

# Privacy Policy - Link Exchange at LinkExchanged! - Link Trade, swap links and more. Service Brought To You By LinkExchanged! Internet Marketing Services

**Security**  
LinkExchanged Internet Marketing services uses the services of Verisign for all monetary Internet transactions.

**Personal Information**  
We only request necessary information on contact / support / member forms. We do not ask for any information for the purpose of passing information to third party services or marketing firms. All information gathered is property of LinkExchanged Internet Marketing Services. Link exchange requests may be distributed to Biznizmen.com for the purpose of exchanging links with users.

**Information Gathered**  
All personal information entered in forms is used to contact users with questions or concerns. Your information will not be shared with outside parties and will only be used to solve problems or contact you. LinkExchanged may track website referrals, web browsers, IP information for statistical purposes only. We will use these information to track patterns troughout our site.

**Links to other Sites**  
LinkExchanged will contain links to other sites (advertisers and affiliates). We are not in any way responsible for the content, security, or privacy maintained in third party sites. 

Please understand this Privacy Statement may change at any time. We will notify members of major changes 1 week in advance.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact us via our online contact form. We will gladly answer any questions you may have.
